Guide to the Service Employees International Union Local 585 Records, 1966-1989 AIS.1982.14
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Collection Additions, II.
  - California School District - Dues Check-Off, 1978-1979 (Box 84, Folder 10)
  - Building Services Inc. - Dues Check-Off, 1978-1979 (Box 84, Folder 11)
  - California State College- Dues Check-Off, 1978-1979 (Box 84, Folder 12)
  - Carmichaels School District - Dues Check-Off, 1978-1979 (Box 84, Folder 13)
  - Curry Memorial Home - Dues Check-Off, 1978-1979 (Box 84, Folder 14)
  - Canon McMillan School District - Dues Check-Off, 1978-1979 (Box 84, Folder 15)
  - The Edward J. Debartolo Corporation - Dues Check-Off, 1978-1979 (Box 84, Folder 16)
  - Henry Clay Frick Community Hospital - Dues Check-Off, 1978-1979 (Box 84, Folder 17)
  - Allegheny County - Dues Check-Off, July 1980 - Dec 1981 (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - Allegheny County - Court House - Dues Check-Off, July 1980 - December 1981 (Box 85, Folder 2-3)
  - Monsour Medical Center - Dues Check-Off, July 1980 - December 1981 (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Allegheny County - Terminations - Monthly Report of Personnel Action, 1981 (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Westmoreland County - Dues Check-Off, July 1980 - December 1981 (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - Washington County - Dues Check-Off, July 1980 - December 1981 (Box 86, Folder 2)
  - Johnstown School District - Dues Check-Off, July 1980 - December 1981 (Box 86, Folder 3)
  - Armstrong Hospital - Election #1 - Legal Case, August 1972 (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - AHA Standard - Job Descriptions - Job Description and Organizational Analysis for Hospitals, 1972 (Box 87, Folder 2)
  - Columbia Hospital - Grievance Cases, Letters, Notices, 1975 (Box 87, Folder 3)
  - Columbia Hospital - Mailings, 1974-1975 (Box 87, Folder 4)
  - Columbia Hospital - Legal File, 1975 (Box 87, Folder 5)
  - Community Health Association of Pennsylvania - Newsletter (Box 87, Folder 6)
  - Evergreen Nursing Home - Legal - NLRB Cases, 1973-1978 (Box 87, Folder 7)
  - Frick Hospital - Legal - NLRB Cases, 1977-1978 (Box 87, Folder 8)
  - Greene County Memorial Hospital - Contract Negotiations and Agreement, 1977-1979 (Box 87, Folder 9)
  - Jeannette Hospital - Unfair Labor Practices - Legal Cases, 1974-1975 (Box 87, Folder 10)
  - Jeannette Hospital - Legal, 1973 (Box 87, Folder 11)
  - Jeannette Hospital (Box 87, Folder 12)
  - SEIU Local 352 - 172 Notice, Letter, 1972-1973 (Box 87, Folder 13)
  - Lutheran Home for the Aged - Code 122 - NLRB Legal Cases, Employee Authorization for SEIU Negotiation, Mailing Lists, 1971-1972 (Box 87, Folder 14)
  - Mt. View Medical Facilities - Legal Cases, 1976 (Box 87, Folder 15)
  - Pennsylvania State Election - Legal Cases, Newspaper Clippings, 1971 (Box 87, Folder 16)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Working Papers - Financial Statements, 1973-1977 (Box 87, Folder 17)
  - Washington School District - Contract Agreements, 1973, 1975-1976 (Box 87, Folder 18)
  - West Allegheny Hospital - Code 167 - NLRB Legal Cases, Notices, Newspaper Clippings, 1972-1973 (Box 87, Folder 19)
  - West Allegheny Hospital - Mailing List (Box 87, Folder 20)
  - West Allegheny Hospital - Legal Case, 1972-1973 (Box 87, Folder 21)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Newspaper Clippings, Research Papers, Notices, 1973-1976, 1980 (Box 87, Folder 22)
  - Babcock - Contract Negotiations, NLRB Cases, Letters, 1972-1973 (Box 88, Folder 1)
  - Old Republic Insurance Co. - Secretarial Code 003 - NLRB Legal Cases, Mailing Lists, Authorization for SEIU Membership, 1973 (Box 88, Folder 2)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Steward Training Class - Letters, Questionnaires, Grievance Cases, 1977 (Box 88, Folder 3)
  - SEIU Local 666 - Training Class - History of Labor Union, Labor Law, Arbitration Materials, 1977 (Box 88, Folder 4)
  - Ralph McDonald - Legal Case for McDonald Grievance, 1979-1981 (Box 88, Folder 5)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Elections - Mailing List of Nominations and Elections, October 1976 (Box 88, Folder 6)
  - SEIU Local 585 - List of Active Members, October 1979 (Box 88, Folder 7)
  - SEIU 1199 - Third Annual Pennsylvania State Wide Professional Conference - Research, Reports, Letters, Notices, 1979 (Box 88, Folder 8)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Research Papers, Political Information, Notices (Box 88, Folder 9)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Audit, 1970-1972 (Box 89, Folder 1)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Bellush Arbitration, 1979 (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Confidential - Research, Reports, Letters, 1978, 1980 (Box 89, Folder 3)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Dues Deduction Authorization Forms (Box 89, Folder 4)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Expense Reports, 1972 (Box 89, Folder 5)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Employment Application, 1970 (Box 89, Folder 6)
  - Cancer Insurance Applications - Correspondence, 1971 (Box 89, Folder 7)
  - Hopewell Industries - Mailing Lists (Box 89, Folder 8)
  - Hopewell Industries - Code 65 - Letters, SEIU Membership Applications, Authorization to Negotiate (Box 89, Folder 9)
  - Mark Lines, Inc. - Mailing List (Box 89, Folder 10)
  - Mark Lines, Inc. - Grievance/Arbitration Cases, Notices, Letters, Authorization to Negotiate with SEIU, 1972 (Box 89, Folder 11)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Organizing Expense Reports, 1971-1972 (Box 89, Folder 11)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Postage - Reports & Correspondence on SEIU Postage Expense, 1972-1973 (Box 89, Folder 12)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Part Time Help - Report of Part Time Employees, 1971-1972 (Box 89, Folder 13)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Questions - PSEA Campaigns (Box 89, Folder 14)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Quarterly Tax Federal Form 941, 1969-1971 (Box 89, Folder 15)
  - SEIU - Welfare Reform Position - Research Papers, Letters, Reports, 1977 (Box 89, Folder 16)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Contract Surveys, Financial Reports, 1972, 1977-1979 (Box 89, Folder 17)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Labor Research (Box 89, Folder 18)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Lobbying Research, 1974-1975 (Box 89, Folder 19)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Welfare Reform Testimony, April 1978 (Box 89, Folder 20)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Dues Ledger, June 1975 (Box 89, Folder 21)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Clerical Job Information (Box 89, Folder 22)
  - AFL-CIO - Notice/Newsletter, 1975 (Box 90, Folder 1)
  - AFL-CIO - Correspondence, 1976 (Box 90, Folder 2)
  - Allegheny County Labor Council - COPE - Notices, 1976 (Box 90, Folder 3)
  - Blue Cross/Blue Shield - Correspondence and Invoice, 1978-1979 (Box 90, Folder 4)
  - COPE - Correspondence, 1975 (Box 90, Folder 5)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Death Gratuities - Paid, 1978-1979, 1974 (Box 90, Folder 6-7)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Fair Share Plan - Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 90, Folder 8)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Form Letters, 1972 (Box 90, Folder 9)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Ineligibles - Correspondence about Death Gratuities, 1978-1979 (Box 90, Folder 10)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Officers - Mailing List, 1976 (Box 90, Folder 11)
  - Louisiana AFL-CIO - Correspondence, 1976 (Box 90, Folder 12)
  - Allegheny County - SEIU Monthly Mailing List - Correspondence, 1972 (Box 90, Folder 13)
  - SEIU - News Releases, 1976 (Box 90, Folder 14)
  - SEIU - Pension Fund - Correspondence and Reports, 1974-1975 (Box 90, Folder 15)
  - SEIU National Industry Pension Fund - Correspondence, 1977 (Box 90, Folder 16)
  - SEIU - Pension Fund - Correspondence and Reports, 1978-1979 (Box 90, Folder 17)
  - SEIU - Subsidy - Correspondence and Reports on SEIU Subsidy to Local 585, 1975-1979 (Box 90, Folder 18)
  - SEIU Joint Council - COPE - Correspondence, 1975-1977 (Box 90, Folder 19)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Senior Member Withdrawal Fund - Correspondence, Reports on Quarterly Tax Refund, 1977-1979 (Box 90, Folder 20)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Stewards' Master Labels - Mailing List (Box 90, Folder 21)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Stewards' Certificates - Copies and Conference Attendance Forms, 1973 (Box 90, Folder 22)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Counterfoil of Rent Check from PA Joint Council #45, 1977, 1979 (Box 90, Folder 23)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Penn Center - Correspondence, 1971-1974 (Box 90, Folder 24)
  - United Way - Mailing List (Box 90, Folder 25)
  - Wholesale Furniture - Correspondence, 1973-1974 (Box 90, Folder 26)
  - Allegheny County Labor Council - Meeting Notice - 2 Copies, 1975 (Box 90, Folder 27)
  - AFL-CIO - Council of Unions for Professional Employees - Brochure and Information, 1976 (Box 90, Folder 28)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Correspondence, 1974-1980 (Box 90, Folder 29)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Auto Insurance and Lease Information - Letters and Records of Auto Insurance, 1972-1973 (Box 91, Folder 1)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Bank Information - Correspondence Pertaining to SEIU Accounts, 1971-1972 (Box 91, Folder 2)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Bonding Company - Letters and Records of Insurance Bonds (Box 91, Folder 3)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Unsigned Contract Agreement (Box 91, Folder 4)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Correspondence from International, 1976-1977 (Box 91, Folder 5-8)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Negotiations Meeting Request Letter, 1971-1972 (Box 91, Folder 9)
  - AFL-CIO - 18th Constitutional Convention - Presidential Address, Election Materials, Convention Bulletin, 1977 (Box 91, Folder 10)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Staff Meetings - Agenda, Minutes, Notices, Reports, Grievance Cases, 1976-1977 (Box 91, Folder 11)
  - SEIU - Labor Reports, 1976 (Box 91, Folder 12)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Death Gratuities, 1972-1973 (Box 91, Folder 13)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Pension Fund - Records, 1973 (Box 91, Folder 14)
  - SEIU Local 585 - PSSU Reinbs - Correspondence and Changes, 1972 (Box 91, Folder 15)
  - SEIU/AFL-CIO - Convention Materials - Reports, Research, Notices, 1973-1976 (Box 91, Folder 16)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Local Meeting - Minutes, Letters, Notices, 1976-1977 (Box 91, Folder 17)
  - Building Services, Inc. - Contract - Signed, 1978-1980 (Box 92, Folder 1)
  - Building Services, Inc. - Contract - Working Copy, 1976 (Box 92, Folder 2)
  - Conrail YMCA - Contract Agreement - Signed Copy, 1979-1982 (Box 92, Folder 3)
  - SEIU - Convention - Resolutions, 1977 (Box 92, Folder 4)
  - SEIU - Convention - Correspondence, 1977 (Box 92, Folder 5)
  - SEIU - Convention - Material Distributed, 1977 (Box 92, Folder 6)
  - SEIU - Convention - Credentials, 1977 (Box 92, Folder 7)
  - SEIU - Convention - Minutes, 1977 (Box 92, Folder 8)
  - SEIU - Convention - Hotel Arrangements, 1977 (Box 92, Folder 9)
  - SEIU - Convention - Agenda and Roll Call, 1977 (Box 92, Folder 10)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Executive Board and Gen. Membership Meetings - Minutes and Information, 1977 (Box 92, Folder 11)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Expense Reports, 1972 (Box 92, Folder 12)
  - SEIU Local 585 - FICA & W/T Form 501 - Monthly Tax Reports, 1972-1973 (Box 92, Folder 13)
  - GPS Investors - Contract - Signed, 1976 (Box 92, Folder 14)
  - GPS Investors - Contract - Old, 1973, 1975, 1981 (Box 92, Folder 15)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Job Classification - Reports, Research Papers, Notices, Chapter Policies (Box 92, Folder 16)
  - Plum School District - Legal Fact Finding, 1974-1975 (Box 92, Folder 17)
  - SEIU Local 585 - President's Executive Board Meeting Notes - Agenda and Minutes, 1975 (Box 92, Folder 18)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Staffing Schedule (Box 92, Folder 19)
  - SEIU Local 585 - State Employment Taxes - Monthly, 1970-1973 (Box 92, Folder 20)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Sub-Work Contract Forms, 1970 (Box 92, Folder 21)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Uniform Price List, 1971 (Box 92, Folder 22)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Workmen's Compensation Act Revisions, 1973-1976 (Box 92, Folder 23)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Steward Training Program - Job Description, Duties, Training Materials, 1976-1978 (Box 92, Folder 24-26)
  - SEIU Local 585 - New Member Orientation (Box 92, Folder 27)
  - Angleoff - Election Challenge - Correspondence, 1973 (Box 93, Folder 1)
  - Angeloff & Trevellini - Dual Unionism Charges - Letters and Notices, 1973 (Box 93, Folder 2)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Appreciation Cards - Funerals, Etc., 1973 (Box 93, Folder 3)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Business Agents - Weekly Reports, 1972 (Box 93, Folder 4)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Bonding File, 1971 (Box 93, Folder 5)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Letter to Credit Union National Association Inc., 1973 (Box 93, Folder 6)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Computer Dimensions - Correspondence, 1972-1974 (Box 93, Folder 7)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Contract Information - Explanations of Collective Bargaining, Agreements, 1971-1973 (Box 93, Folder 8)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Dental Plans - Pamphlets Explaining Dental Planning, 1971-1973 (Box 93, Folder 9)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Escape Tours - Correspondence, 1974 (Box 93, Folder 10)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Equal Pay - Letters, Pamphlets, 1972 (Box 93, Folder 11)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Executive Board Minutes, 1972 (Box 93, Folder 12)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Eye Care Plans - Letters, Pamphlets, 1973-1975 (Box 93, Folder 13)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Control Reports, 1973 (Box 93, Folder 14)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Officers - Letters Pertaining to Legal Expenses, 1973 (Box 93, Folder 15)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Meeting Hall Correspondence, 1973 (Box 93, Folder 16)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Mediators - Correspondence About Labor Disputes, 1974 (Box 93, Folder 17)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Officer's Installation Oath, 1970-1971 (Box 93, Folder 18)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Organizing Leads - Correspondence, 1973 (Box 93, Folder 19)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Surveys - Correspondence About Health Surveys, 1973 (Box 93, Folder 20)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Special Funds - Financial Statements, 1978 (Box 93, Folder 21)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Senior Member Material - Convention Reports, Pamphlets, 1980 (Box 93, Folder 22)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Meeting and Strike Notices, 1970-1974 (Box 93, Folder 23)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Clerical-Technical - Pamphlets, Buttons (Box 93, Folder 24)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Pension - Correspondence and Records of Pension Remittance, 1977 (Box 93, Folder 25)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Death Gratuities, Pending - Correspondence, 1977 (Box 93, Folder 26)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Ivory, Wagner, and Nugent - Insurance Appraisals Reports, 1977 (Box 93, Folder 27)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Death Gratuities, Paid - Correspondence, 1977 (Box 93, Folder 28)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Brooks - Memo for Filing Tax Reports, 1977 (Box 93, Folder 29)
  - SEIU - Convention Research, 1978 (Box 93, Folder 30)
  - SEIU - 20th Convention Materials - Reports, Pamphlets, Notices, 1979 (Box 93, Folder 31)
  - SEIU - 4th Convention Materials - Reports, Notices, Newsletters, 1979 (Box 93, Folder 32)
  - Canonsburg General Hospital - Grievance Cases, 1976-1978 (Box 94, Folder 1)
  - Hospitals - NLRB Correspondence and Petitions, 1976-1980 (Box 94, Folder 2)
  - Indiana Hospital - Code 155 - General Correspondence and Notices, 1972-1973 (Box 94, Folder 3)
  - Pittsburgh Ways - Sketches of Pittsburgh Roads (Box 94, Folder 4)
  - Oil City Hospital - Correspondence and Grievances, 1973-1976 (Box 94, Folder 5)
  - Oil City Hospital - Mailing List, 1974 (Box 94, Folder 6)
  - Oil City Hospital - Pre-Election Info, 1973 (Box 94, Folder 7)
  - Oil City Hospital - Post-Election Info, 1973 (Box 94, Folder 8)
  - SEIU Hospital - Copies of Amended Petition, 1974 (Box 94, Folder 9)
  - West Penn Hospital - Mailing List and Grievance, 1978 (Box 94, Folder 9)
  - SEIU Local 585 - NLRB Grievance Cases, 1976-1979 (Box 94, Folder 10)
  - West Penn Hospital - Mailing List (Box 94, Folder 11)
  - Magee Womens' Hospital - Grievance Cases, 1975 (Box 94, Folder 12)
  - Greene County Memorial Hospital - Memos and Petition, 1974 (Box 94, Folder 13)
  - McKeesport Hospital - Grievance Cases, 1974-1981 (Box 94, Folder 14)
  - SEIU Local 585 - NLRB Grievance Cases, 1974, 1979 (Box 94, Folder 15)
  - Conemaugh Valley Memorial Hospital - Grievance Case and Contract Negotiations, 1974 (Box 94, Folder 16)
  - Beaver County Hospital - Letters, Notices, Newspaper Clippings, 1974 (Box 94, Folder 17)
  - Central Medical Pavilion - Information, 1974 (Box 94, Folder 18)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Info - Labor Activities/Conditions in Hospitals, 1973-1974 (Box 94, Folder 19)
  - Montefiore Hospital - Grievance Case, 1976 (Box 94, Folder 20)
  - Presbyterian Hospital - Contract Agreement, 1974 (Box 94, Folder 21)
  - St. Clair Memorial Hospital - Tax Exemption Newspaper Clipping (Box 94, Folder 22)
  - St. Francis General Hospital - Grievance Case, 1974 (Box 94, Folder 23)
  - Westmoreland Hospital Association - Grievance Cases, 1974, 1979 (Box 94, Folder 24)
  - Brownsville General Hospital - Grievance Case, 1974 (Box 94, Folder 25)
  - Allegheny Valley Hospital - Grievance Cases and Mailing List, 1976-1977 (Box 94, Folder 26)
  - Allegheny General Hospital - News Clippings Pertaining to Labor Relations, 1974, 1981 (Box 94, Folder 27)
  - Aliquippa Hospital - Grievance Cases, 1972, 1979 (Box 94, Folder 28)
  - SEIU Local 585 - NLRB Cases - Hospital Grievance Cases, 1975-1981 (Box 94, Folder 29)
  - SEIU Local 686 - Gas Workers - The Pilot - One Copy, 1977 (Box 95, Folder 1)
  - SEIU Local 36 - Minutes of Executive Meetings, Local 36 News, 1977 (Box 95, Folder 2)
  - SEIU - Local News - Affiliate News, 1974-1976 (Box 95, Folder 3)
  - Pennsylvania AFL-CIO - Political Action - Volunteers in Politics (Box 95, Folder 4)
  - Pennsylvania Social Services Union - Strike Materials - News Clippings, Notices, Press Release, 1977 (Box 95, Folder 5)
  - SEIU - State Council Papers - Back-Up Issues - PA Service Employee News, 1975 (Box 95, Folder 6)
  - Westmoreland County - Correspondence, 1978-1980 (Box 95, Folder 7)
  - Westmoreland County - Contract Agreement and List of Employees - Working Copy, 1973 (Box 95, Folder 8)
  - Westmoreland County - Negotiations - News Clipping, Mailing List, Meeting Minutes, 1981 (Box 95, Folder 9)
  - Westmoreland County - Supervisors - Correspondence, 1973-1974, 1977-1980 (Box 95, Folder 10)
  - Westmoreland County - Personnel Changes - Adds, Drops, etc., 1975 (Box 95, Folder 11)
  - Westmoreland County - Correspondence, 1974-1979 (Box 95, Folder 12)
  - Westmoreland County - Strike - Correspondence on Union Fees Deductions, 1980-1981 (Box 95, Folder 13)
  - Wobblie Joe's - Contract Agreement, 1979 (Box 95, Folder 14)
  - SEIU - Hospital NLRB Guidelines, 1973-1974 (Box 95, Folder 15)
  - SEIU - Eastern Conference of Service Employee Unions, 1975 (Box 95, Folder 16)
  - Greater Johnstown School District - Contract - Working Copy, 1978 (Box 96, Folder 1)
  - Johnstown School District - Contract Negotiations and Agreement - Working Copy, 1976-1978 (Box 96, Folder 2)
  - Johnstown School District - Legal - Grievance Cases, Contract Agreements, Memos, Notices, 1975-1979 (Box 96, Folder 3)
  - Johnstown School District - Correspondence, 1975-1978 (Box 96, Folder 4)
  - Johnstown School District - Non-Members - Mailing List of Union and Non-Union Members (Box 96, Folder 5)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Daybook of Receipts and Expenditures, 1969-1974 (Box 96, Folder 6-7)
  - Johnstown School District - Check Book of Employee's Association - Local 662 (Box 96, Folder 8)
  - SEIU Ontario Provincial Joint Council #22 Annual Seminar - Reports and Research Papers (Box 96, Folder 9)
  - Allegheny County - Blue Collar - Dues Check-Off, 1972-1973 (Box 97, Folder 1)
  - Allegheny County - Clerical-Technical Unit - Dues Check-Off (Box 97, Folder 2)
  - Allegheny Valley - Dues Check-Off, 1970-1973 (Box 97, Folder 3)
  - Albert Gallatin - Dues Check-Off, 1972-1973 (Box 97, Folder 4)
  - Armstrong County School District - Dues Check-Off, 1970-1972 (Box 97, Folder 5-6)
  - Apollo Ridge - Dues Check-Off, 1972-1973 (Box 97, Folder 7)
  - Avonworth - Dues Check-Off, 1972-1973 (Box 97, Folder 8)
  - Beaver County - Dues Check-Off, 1973 (Box 97, Folder 9)
  - Blair County - Dues Check-Off, 1972 (Box 97, Folder 10)
  - Bethel Park - Dues Check-Off, 1972 (Box 97, Folder 11)
  - Brownsville Area School District - Dues Check-Off, 1971-1973 (Box 97, Folder 12)
  - Building Services - Dues Check-Off, 1972-1973 (Box 97, Folder 13)
  - Burrell School District - Dues Check-Off, 1971-1973 (Box 97, Folder 14)
  - Butler Area School District - Dues Check-Off, 1973-1974 (Box 97, Folder 15)
  - California - Dues Check-Off, 1972 (Box 97, Folder 16)
  - Canon-McMillan - Dues Check-Off, 1971-1973 (Box 97, Folder 17)
  - Carlynton School District - Dues Check-Off, 1973 (Box 97, Folder 18)
  - Carmichaels - Dues Check-Off, 1972 (Box 97, Folder 19)
  - Churchill Area School District - Dues Check-Off, 1969-1973 (Box 97, Folder 20-21)
  - Curry Home - Dues Check-Off, 1972-1973 (Box 97, Folder 22)
  - Connellsville - Dues Check-Off, 1971 (Box 97, Folder 23)
  - Cranberry Area School District - Dues Check-Off, 1973-1974 (Box 97, Folder 24)
  - Deer Lakes - Dues Check-Off, 1971-1973 (Box 97, Folder 25)
  - Dubois Area School District - Dues Check-Off, 1971-1973 (Box 97, Folder 26)
  - East Allegheny - Dues Check-Off, 1970-1972 (Box 97, Folder 27)
  - Elizabeth Forward - Dues Check-Off, 1972 (Box 97, Folder 28)
  - Elwood City - Dues Check-Off, 1970-1973 (Box 97, Folder 29)
  - Fayette County - Dues Check-Off, 1972-1973 (Box 97, Folder 30)
  - Forest Hills - Dues Check-Off, 1972-1973 (Box 97, Folder 31)
  - Franklin Area School District - Dues Check-Off, 1972-1973 (Box 97, Folder 32-33)
  - General Braddock School District - Dues Check-Off, 1972 (Box 97, Folder 34)
  - Gateway School District - Dues Check-Off, 1971-1973 (Box 97, Folder 35)
  - Glassport - Dues Check-Off, 1971-1972 (Box 97, Folder 36)
  - Greene County Memorial Hospital - Dues Check-Off, 1972-1973 (Box 97, Folder 37)
  - Hamar Township - Dues Check-Off, 1973 (Box 97, Folder 38)
  - Highlands School District - Dues Check-Off, 1970-1972 (Box 97, Folder 39)
  - Indiana Township - Dues Check-Off, 1973 (Box 97, Folder 40)
  - Jefferson-Morgan - Dues Check-Off, 1973 (Box 97, Folder 41)
  - Keystone Oaks - Dues Check-Off, 1971-1973 (Box 97, Folder 42)
  - Kiski - Dues Check-Off, 1971-1972 (Box 97, Folder 43)
  - Leechburg - Dues Check-Off, 1971-1973 (Box 97, Folder 44)
  - Local 264 - Gallatin National Bank - Dues Check-Off, 1972-1973 (Box 97, Folder 45)
  - Mt. Pleasant - Dues Check-Off, 1971-1973 (Box 97, Folder 46)
  - New Kinsington-Arnold - Dues Check-Off, 1971-1973 (Box 97, Folder 47-48)
  - North Braddock Borough - Dues Check-Off, 1972-1973 (Box 97, Folder 49)
  - North Hills - Dues Check-Off, 1972-1973 (Box 97, Folder 50)
  - North Star School District - Dues Check-Off, 1973 (Box 97, Folder 51)
  - Penn Trafford - Dues Check-Off, 1971-1973 (Box 97, Folder 52)
  - Oil City School District - Dues Check-Off, 1972-1974 (Box 97, Folder 53)
  - Peters Township - Dues Check-Off, 1972-1973 (Box 97, Folder 54)
  - SEIU - Summer Dues - Mailing List, 1974 (Box 97, Folder 55)
  - Plum Borough - Dues Check-Off, 1970-1973 (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Portage - Dues Check-Off, 1972-1973 (Box 98, Folder 2)
  - South Butler - Dues Check-Off, 1971-1973 (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - Southeastern Green - Dues Check-Off, 1971-1972 (Box 98, Folder 4)
  - Southmoreland - Dues Check-Off, 1971-1973 (Box 98, Folder 5)
  - South Park - Dues Check-Off, 1971 (Box 98, Folder 6)
  - Sunnyview Nursing Home - Dues Check-Off, 1973-1974 (Box 98, Folder 7)
  - Toner Institute - Dues Check-Off, 1973 (Box 98, Folder 8)
  - Trinity Area School District - Dues Check-Off, 1972-1973 (Box 98, Folder 9)
  - Turtle Creek - Dues Check-Off, 1971 (Box 98, Folder 10)
  - City of Washington - Dues Check-Off, 1973 (Box 98, Folder 11)
  - Washington - Dues Check-Off, 1971 (Box 98, Folder 12)
  - Wilkinsburg - Dues Check-Off, 1971-1972 (Box 98, Folder 13)
  - West Deer Municipal - Dues Check-Off, 1971-1973 (Box 98, Folder 14)
  - West Mifflin - Dues Check-Off, 1972-1973 (Box 98, Folder 15)
  - Westmoreland County - Dues Check-Off, 1972-1973 (Box 98, Folder 16)
  - Westmoreland Intermediate Unit - Dues Check-Off, 1972 (Box 98, Folder 17)
  - White Oak Borough Authority - Dues Check-Off, 1973 (Box 98, Folder 18)
  - Borough of Wilkinsburg - Dues Check-Off, 1972 (Box 98, Folder 19)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Chapter Officers and Stewards - Mailing Lists (Box 99, Folder 1)